Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Travenol Laboratories, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: Employee Performance Appraisal Summary, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
    By Travelers Insurance. Annual Salaried. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Travels Annual Salaried Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
    By Travelers Insurance. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Employee Performance Appraisal Summary, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
    By Travelers Insurance. Weekly Salaried and Hourly Paid. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Travelers Weekly Salaried-Horly Paid Performance Proposal, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 19: Work Simplification For Supervisors, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 20: Effective Business Meetings, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 21: Written Skills, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 22: Delegation For Supervisors, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 23: Effective Presentations, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 24: Employee Development, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 25: Employment Interviewing Techniques, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 26: General Development Skills, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 27: Decision Making, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 28: Business Compostion, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 29: Basic Math, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 30: Office Skills Development Program, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
    By Travelers Insurance. Shorthand. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Office Skills Development Program, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
    By Travelers Insurance. Typing Skills. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Writing Skills Workshop, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 33: Home Office Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 34: The History of Insurance In America Reads Like, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
    By Travelers Insurance. A History of The Travelers. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: The Travelers Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
    By Travelers Insurance. Newsletter. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Data Processing Careers At The Travelers, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
    By Travelers Insurance. Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: The Travelers: Older Americans Program, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
    By Travelers Corporation. Folder cointaining information. Item is in English.
- TruCare, Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Travenol: Perspectives, Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
    By Travenol Laboratories. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
- Twentieth Century Fund - House Organs, Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Your Employees Deserve Employee Assistance Programs, Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
    By TruCare. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Your Employees Deserve Employee Assistance Programs, Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
    By TruCare. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Ullico - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Newsletter, Publication (Box 29, Folder 18)
    By Twentieth Century Fund. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Nwesletter, Publication (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Newsletter, Publication (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Newsletter, Publication (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Newsletter, Publication (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Ullico - House Organs, Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
    By Ullico. News Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
    By Ullico. News Booklet - August 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
    By Ullico. News Booklet: August, 1992 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
    By Ullico. News booklet - March-April, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
    By Ullico. News Booklet 1989. Item is in English.
- Unemployment Compensation Commission, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. August-September, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.3, 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.3, 1982 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. june-July, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. May 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. October 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. December 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. April 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.2, 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.4, 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. no.1,1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.2, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.1, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.2,1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.3,1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No. 3, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.3, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No. 4, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No. 2, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No. 1, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 1, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 2, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 3, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.4, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.4, 1986 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.2, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.2, 1987 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.3, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.3, 1987 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Item 32: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.1, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. No.2, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 2, 1988 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: True to Our Mission: Annual Report, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Union Labor Life Insurance. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Money at Work, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. July 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Money At Work, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. July 1988 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 1,1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 1, 1989 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 2, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 2, 1989 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 3, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 3, 1989 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 1, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 1, 1990 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 2-3, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Item 48: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 4, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 4, 1990 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Letter, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Daniel E. Sullivan. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Resource Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. The Magazine for Life Insurance Management - January 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 5, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 5, 1990 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: 1989 Annual Report, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 6, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 6, 1990 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 1, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 1, 1991 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 3, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 60: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 3, 1991 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. number 5, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 62: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 5,1991 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Item 64: Bulletin, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    By Ullico. Number 1, 1992. Item is in English.
- Union Carbide Corporation - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Information for Workers: Unemployment Compensation in New Jersey, Publication (Box 29, Folder 21)
    By Unemployment Compensation Commission. Item is in English.
- Union Democracy, Association for, 1998; Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Surgical Medical, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Retirement Program, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Dental Expense Assistance Plan, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Hospital Insurance, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: Annual Performace Appraisal, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Form. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Perspectives: On Crticial Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. The Business of Black America. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Perspectives: On Critical Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Starting Over, Again: Rethinking U.S. Water Quality Programs. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Resources and Responsibility. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. How to Stop Talking About Industrial Wastes and Do Something About Them. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Industrial Development's New Dimension. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Strategic Competitveness. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Planning for Energy Emergencies. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. A Petrochemical Perspective. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Chemicals From Petroleum. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Plans and Policies, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. A Worksheet for I.A.s. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Making the most of..Your International Assignment, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 19: Product Directory 1981, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 20: Electronic Division Profile, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. October 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: UCC Gets Good Reviews, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: HQNews, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 23: Union Carbide, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 24: Public Policy Agenda 1984, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Union Carbide Chemicals and Plastics, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 26: We Exist For Our Customers, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 27: Corporate Placement Service, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Internal/External Job Search Workbook. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Special Report, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. News Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: You and Union Carbide: A Strong Partnership, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Union Labor Life Insurance Company, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Ulico Casualty Company, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Union labor Life Insurance Co. 1990 Annual Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 1990 Annual Report, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Union labor Life Insurance Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: 1989 Annual Report, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: 1988 Annual Report, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: 1989 Annual Report, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Union labor Life Insurance Co. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: WDL News, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Workers Defense League. Newsletter - Spring 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Bulletin, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Ullico. Number 2, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Bulletin, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Ullico. November 2, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Bulletin, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Ullico. August 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Bulletin, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Ullico. August, 1992 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Bulletin, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Ullico. December, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Bulletin, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Ullico. December, 1992 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: News Release, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Union labor Life Insurance Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: News Release, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Union labor Life Insurance Company. December 21, 1999. Item is in English.
- United Labor Service Agency, Publication (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: United Labor Service Agency, Publication (Box 30, Folder 2)
    By United Labor Service Agency. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Uniroyal, Inc. - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 1980 Directory of Products and Services, Publication (Box 30, Folder 3)
    By Uniroyal. Item is in English.
- Union Pacific Corporation - EAP Activity Report, 1972-1986; Publication (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Activity Report: 1972-1986, Publication (Box 30, Folder 4)
    By Union Pacific Corporation. Item is in English.
- UNISYS Infor, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - March, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - January, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - January, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - Number 3, May, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - June, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - October 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - November, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - December, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - May, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - August 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - No. 5 - Oct./Nov. 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - January, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - Feburary, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - July, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - April, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - November, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - December, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - No. 1 - March, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - July, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - September, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - No.4, November, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - No. 4, Feburary 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - Vol.6, No. 2, June 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper -Vol. 6, No. 3, August 1991. Item is in English.
- United Brands Company - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York Office Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 30, Folder 6)
    By United Brands. Febuary 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: United Brands and Costa Rica- A closer look, Publication (Box 30, Folder 6)
    By United Brands. Newsletter - May 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: United Brands and Panama- A closer look, Publication (Box 30, Folder 6)
    By United Brands. Newsletter - July 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: United Brands and Honduras- A closer look, Publication (Box 30, Folder 6)
    By United Brands. Newsletter - June 1981. Item is in English.
- United States. Air Force. Saratoga Air Force Station, Publication (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Intinerary Card for an event, Publication (Box 30, Folder 7)
    By United States Airforce Saratoga Airforce Station. Dining Out - 18 March 1972. Item is in English.
- United States. Commission on Civil Rights, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Political Activity of Federal Officers and Employees, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
    By U.S. Civil Service Commission. Pamphlet 66. Item is in English.
- United States. Congress. Office of Technology Assessment, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
    By United States Commission on Civil Rights. September 1980. Item is in English.
- United States Dept. of the Army, Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Plant Closing: Advance Notice and Rapid Response, Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
    By United States Congress. Office of Technology Assessment. September 1986. Item is in English.
- U.S. Department of Commerce - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Employee Services and Quality of Worklife, Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
    By U.S. Dept. of the Army. February 1984. Item is in English.
- DOL, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Statement of the Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Department of Commerce. February 3, 1981 - By: Eric J. Oxfeld. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Simple Exterior Can Contain Suprising Things, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Department of Commerce. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Performance Plan, Progress Review & Appraisal Record, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Department of Commerce. Form. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Simple Exterior Can Contain Suprising Things, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Department of Commerce. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Department of Commerce. November, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Emergency and Permanent Policies of Spreading Work in Industrial Employment, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    By The President's Emergency Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: A Manager's Guide to Taking Adverse Actions, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Department of Commerce. June 1984. Item is in English.
- United States. Dept. of Labor, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Wartime Reminders to Women Who Work, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. January 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Workmen's Compensation: The Benefits, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Foreman's Guide to Labor Relations, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: The Women's Bureau of the U.S. Department of Labor, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. August 1941. Item is in English.